Guide to the American Association of Advertising Agencies Records, 1918-1998
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
American Association of Advertising Agencies records 1918-1998
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
American Association of Advertising Agencies
45 linear feet Extent: 67,000 Items
The American Association of Advertising Agencies, founded in 1917, is the primary advertising industry trade organization. The American Association of Advertising Agencies (AAAA) Records span the years 1918-1998 and include correspondence, annual corporate and stockholder reports for member agencies, meeting minutes and speeches, biographical summaries, a subject file, and videotapes that document selected activities and functions of the organization. The collection has been compiled from a number of accessions received over time, and so does not represent a comprehensive archive of the AAAA. Certain aspects of AAAA activities, however, are well represented, including a set of card files that document the professional careers of AAAA members over a 50-year period, and subject files that focus on Federal Trade Commission (FTC), Federal Communications Commission (FCC) and the Food and Drug Administration (FDA) investigations into complaints lodged against advertisers and advertising claims produced in a variety of media, with a particular emphasis on the ways that products were advertised during and in conjunction with children's television programming. Other topics touched on include advertising self-regulation, antitrust issues, advertising laws, and deceptive and ethical practices in marketing and advertising.
RL.00003
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is restricted.
Original audiovisual materials are closed to patron use. Use copies are available for some items. Technical Services staff may need to produce use copies before contents can be accessed.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. There may be a 48-hour delay in obtaining these materials.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The American Association of Advertising Agencies Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 1995-2002.
Administrative History
1900 American Advertising Agents' Association
1911 Association of New York Advertising Agents; William H. Johns (George Batten Company and founder of Audit Bureau of Circulations), Chairman
1912-1916 Regional advertising associations
1916 Affiliated Association of Advertising Agencies
1917 American Association of Advertising Agencies (AAAA) formed with 111 charter members and 5 regional councils (New York, Boston, Philadelphia, Chicago, Southern) AAAA instrumental in formation of the Division of Advertising, Committee of Public Information, to support the war effort through recruiting, liberty bond, and Red Cross promotion
1917-1919 William H. Johns, President (position later renamed Chairman)
1917-1927 James O'Shaughnessy, Executive Secretary (position later renamed President)
1918 Agency Service Standards adopted Media Rate Card established to publish and standardize member advertising rates
1919-1928 Advertising Agencies Corporation formed to support the war effort and other public service programs
1920 Standard order blanks, copyright protected forms to document member advertising services
1921 Uniform 15% commission rate; eventually adopted as an industry standard
1924 AAAA Standards of Practice
1926 U.S. President Calvin Coolidge delivered keynote address at the 10th Annual Meeting
1928-1943 John Benson, AAAA President
1931 Creative Code adopted to regulate advertising content
1936 AAAA and Association of National Advertisers (ANA) jointly form the Advertising Research Foundation to foster advertising-related market research
1942 War Advertising Council
1944-1961 Frederic R. Gamble, AAAA President
1945 Committee to Address Objectionable Advertising
1946 AAAA Interchange of Opinion, a forum where members could register complaints of objectionable advertising
1960 AAAA and ANA joint Committee for the Improvement of Advertising Content, aimed at industry self-regulation
1962-1977 John Crichton, AAAA President
1967 AAAA Educational Foundation, to foster advertising-related research at the university level
1971 National Advertising Review Board
1973 Multicultural Advertising Internship Program (MAIP), to encourage minority entry into the advertising profession
1978 William R. Hesse, AAAA President
1979-1988 Leonard S. Matthews, AAAA President
1983 AAAA Educational Foundation and Educational Foundation of the American Advertising Foundation merge to form Advertising Educational Foundation
1986 Media Advertising Partnership for a Drug-Free America
1989-1993 John E. O'Toole, AAAA President
1994-Present O. Burtch Drake, AAAA President
Circa 1995 AAAA and ANA jointly form Coalition for Advertising Supported Information and Entertainment (CASIE) to address issues relating to interactive media and internet advertising, including online privacy
Historical timeline compiled from Marsha Appel, American Association of Advertising Agencies, in Advertising Age Encyclopedia of Advertising (N.Y.: Fitzroy Dearborn, 2003) and other sources.
Collection Overview
The American Association of Advertising Agencies (AAAA) Records spans the years 1918-1998 and includes correspondence, annual corporate and stockholder reports for member agencies, meeting minutes and speeches, biographical summaries, a subject file, and videotapes that document selected activities and functions of the organization. The collection has been compiled from a number of accessions received over time, and so does not represent a comprehensive archive of the AAAA. Certain aspects of AAAA activities, however, are well represented, including the card files that document the professional careers of AAAA members over a 50-year period, and subject files that focus on Federal Trade Commission (FTC), Federal Communications Commission (FCC) and the Food and Drug Administration (FDA) investigations into complaints lodged against advertisers and advertising claims produced in a variety of media, with a particular emphasis on the ways that products were advertised during and in conjunction with children's television programming. Other topics touched on include advertising self-regulation, antitrust issues, advertising laws, and deceptive and ethical practices in marketing and advertising.
The collection is arranged into four series: Administrative Files, Member Card Files, Vertical Files, and Audiovisual Materials. The Administrative Files Series includes correspondence, member corporate annual and stockholder reports, printed materials, meeting minutes and speeches, and memorabilia. The Member Card Files Series contains approximately 46,000 index cards that briefly document the employment histories of individual members roughly between the years 1920 and 1969. The Vertical Files Series consists of an alphabetical subject file primarily focused on FTC, FCC, and FDA hearings on complaints against advertisers as well as documents and testimonies relating to advertising to children. Also included is a compiled set of writings on advertising during times of recession and war. The Audiovisual Materials Series consists primarily of taped interviews with David Ogilvy and William Bernbach. Original videotapes are closed to patron use. Use copies are currently available for some items. Technical Services staff may need to produce use copies before contents can be accessed. Please contact Research Services staff before coming to use the collection.
Related Material
Related materials within the Hartman Center collections include the Outdoor Advertising Association of America (OAAA) Archives, the Bates Worldwide Inc. Records, the J. Walter Thompson Co. Advertising Vertical File, the J. Walter Thompson Co. Information Center Records and the McGraw-Hill Marketing Information Center Records. For materials pertaining to advertising during wartime, see also the War Effort Mobilization Campaigns Poster Collection, the J. Walter Thompson Co. World War II Advertising Collection, the Advertising Council Records, the Charles W. Hoyt Company Records, the R.C. Maxwell Co. Records, the Strobridge Lithographing Company Advertisements, the Howard Scott Papers, and the J. Walter Thompson Co. Publications Collection. For materials relating to television advertising, see also the J. Walter Thompson Co. John Devine Papers, and the D'arcy Masius Benton & Bowles Records. For materials relating to advertising and children, see also the J. Walter Thompson Co. Chicago Office Records Non-Proprietary Research Reports.
Subject Headings
American Association of Advertising Agencies; United States. Federal Communications Commission; United States. Federal Trade Commission; United States. Food and Drug Administration; Advertising -- Moral and ethical aspects; Advertising -- United States -- History; Advertising -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Advertising and children; Advertising laws -- United States; Antitrust law; Corporation reports; Deceptive advertising -- United States; Marketing -- Ethics -- United States; Television advertising; Television advertising and children; Minutes; Speeches; Videotapes; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
Contents of Collection
- Administrative Files Series, 1918-1998, (7 boxes)
  Includes correspondence, reports and other printed materials, meeting minutes and speeches, member agency annual and stockholder reports, and memorabilia. Arranged alphabetically.
  - Advertising awards, 1923-1966, (3 folders) (Box AF1)
  - Agency-client relations, 1972-1976, (1-6 of 9 folders) (Box AF1)
  - Agency-client relations (continued), 1972-1976, (7-9 of 9 folders) (Box AF2)
  - Association publications, 1958-1998
    - Advertising Industry, 1958 (Box AF2)
    - ANA-AAAA Interchange for Objectionable Advertising, 1963-1966 (Box AF2)
    - Newsletters, 1964-1978 (Box AF2)
    - Pamphlets, 1982-1998 (Box AF2)
  - Meetings, 1918-1926, 1976
    - International Advertising Convention (London), 1924, (3 folders) (Box AF2)
    - Minutes, 1918-1924, (3 folders) (Box AF2)
    - Morning Session Report, 1923, (3 folders) (Box AF3)
    - Papers from the annual meeting, 1976 (Box AF3)
    - Reports, 1923, (3 folders) (Box AF3)
    - Speeches (Philadelphia, Washington D.C.), 1926 (Box AF3)
  - Member agency annual reports, 1981-1984, (7 folders) (Box AF4)
  - Member agency annual reports (continued), 1985-1993, (7 folders) (Box AF5)
  - Member agency stock reports, 1987-1992, (1-10 of 18 folders) (Box AF6)
  - Member agency stock reports (continued), 1990-1992, (11-18 of 18 folders) (Box AF7)
  - Memorabilia, 1924
    - Mrs. Mary O'Shaughnessy's Berlin Kongress pin, 1924 (Box AF7)
    - Mrs. Mary O'Shaughnessy's London visit memorabilia, 1924 (Box AF7)
  - Memoranda and articles by John O'Toole, 1968-1985, (2 folders) (Box AF7)
  - Video use copies for OR1, OR3. Created: 2007. Format: DVD. (Box AF7)
- Member Biographical Card File Series, circa 1920-circa 1968, (39 boxes)
  Consists of index cards for member agency employees. A typical card lists the agency name(s) and the position(s) a specific individual held, and the date each position began. Arranged alphabetically by last name.
  - Aalgard--Anwyl (Box CF1)
  - Apatow--Barons (Box CF2)
  - Barr--Bilinsky (Box CF3)
  - Bilker--Brazeau (Box CF4)
  - Breakey--Bury (Box CF5)
  - Busby--Chandler (Box CF6)
  - Chandor--Connolly (Box CF7)
  - Conover--Dampsey (Box CF8)
  - Dana-Dixon (Box CF9)
  - Doak--Egri (Box CF10)
  - Ehler-Fewsmith (Box CF11)
  - Fiandt--Frizzell (Box CF12)
  - Froelich--Gneier (Box CF13)
  - Goad--Grzybowski (Box CF14)
  - Guarch--Hart (Box CF15)
  - Harte--Hill (Box CF16)
  - Hilliard--Humenick (Box CF17)
  - Humm--Jondreau (Box CF18)
  - Jones--Ketchum (Box CF19)
  - Ketner--Lamont (Box CF20)
  - LaMontagne--Limerick (Box CF21)
  - Linabury--Maddux (Box CF22)
  - Madeira--McCoy (Box CF23)
  - McCracken--Metzger (Box CF24)
  - Meulendyke--Morvay (Box CF25)
  - Moscato--Nonne (Box CF26)
  - Noonan--Paryzek (Box CF27)
  - Pas--Postna (Box CF28)
  - Pote--Rettker (Box CF29)
  - Reuben--Ross (Box CF30)
  - Rosse--Schmidt (Box CF31)
  - Schmidtke--Sholle (Box CF32)
  - Sholty--Staley (Box CF33)
  - Stalk--Svoboda (Box CF34)
  - Swackhamer--Towery (Box CF35)
  - Towle--Wadsworth (Box CF36)
  - Waechter--Welge (Box CF37)
  - Wellenkamp--Wilson-Lawrence (Box CF38)
  - Wilt--Zylkowski (Box CF39)
- Vertical Files Series, 1939-1993, bulk 1958-1983, (38 boxes)
  Consists of subject files primarily of printed materials. The bulk of materials represent activities relating to children's television advertising, complaints lodged with the Federal Trade Commission, and efforts at advertising industry self-regulation. Arranged alphabetically by topic.
  - Advertising in times of recession/war, 1939-1976 and undated, (7 folders) (Box VF1)
    A chronological listing of titles appears at the end of the Detailed Description.
  - Antitrust Articles (alphabetical by author), 1969-1981
    - Bass-Telser, (8 folders) (Box VF2)
    - Turner-Z, (3 folders) (Box VF3)
  - Antitrust Industries, 1969-1981
    - Automotive (Box VF3)
    - Media (Box VF3)
    - Oil (Box VF3)
    - Telephone utilities, (3 folders) (Box VF3)
  - Brands
    - Quality Brands Associates of America, 1959-1964 (Box VF3)
  - Children's Television
    - Academic Reports (alphabetical by author), 1969-1981
      - A-Brumbaugh, (6 folders) (Box VF4)
      - Burn-Ferguson, (11 folders) (Box VF5)
      - Fernandez-Lyle, (10 folders) (Box VF6)
      - Mansfield-Scharr, (9 folders) (Box VF7)
      - Shantz-Yankelovich, (7 folders) (Box VF8)
    - Bound materials (alphabetical by author), 1970-1979
      - Atkin-Nielsen, (11 folders) (Box VF9)
      - Sharusa-Wartella, (8 folders) (Box VF10)
    - Clippings
      - 1970-1977, (11 folders) (Box VF11)
      - 1978-1979, (7 folders) (Box VF12)
      - 1980-1991, (11 folders) (Box VF13)
      - Inserts and pamphlets, 1974-1993, (4 folders) (Box VF13)
    - Government regulation
      - FTC hearings
        - Evidence and comments, 1970-1981, (6 folders) (Box VF14)
        - House of Representatives hearings, 1975 (Box VF14)
        - Media reports, 1979 (Box VF14)
        - Modern advertising practices, 1971 (Box VF15)
        - Summaries, 1979, (6 folders) (Box VF15)
        - Testimony, 1970-1981, (6 folders) (Box VF16)
      - Petitions and litigation
        - ANA v. FTC, 1979, (2 folders) (Box VF16)
        - FCC-ACT petition, 1978, (1-2 of 3 folders) (Box VF16)
        - FCC-ACT petition (continued), 1978, (3 of 3 folders) (Box VF17)
        - FCC-Council on Children, 1975 (Box VF17)
        - FTC Orders re: 43 Fed. Reg 17967, 1978 (Box VF17)
        - FCC proposed children's television regulations, 1979-1980 (Box VF17)
        - FTC staff reports, 1978-1981, (3 folders) (Box VF17)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC)
    - Network inquiries, 1977-1981 (Box VF17)
    - Oversight hearings, 1975 (Box VF17)
  - Federal Trade Commission (FTC)
    - General Files
      - General, 1960-1975, (3 folders) (Box VF17)
      - Injunctive powers, 1958-1983, (2 folders) (Box VF18)
    - Complaints, 1958-1983
      - AAMCO Transmissions (Box VF18)
      - Acne treatments (Box VF18)
      - Advertised specials (Box VF18)
      - Aero Wax (Box VF18)
      - Air conditioning (Box VF18)
      - Alcoa (Box VF18)
      - American Dairy Association (Box VF18)
      - American Home Products, (2 folders) (Box VF18)
      - American Models Service (Box VF18)
      - American Tobacco Company (Box VF18)
      - Amstar Corp. (Box VF18)
      - Argus Inc. (Box VF18)
      - Arrivals LTD (Box VF18)
      - Art instruction schools (Box VF18)
    - Complaints, 1958-1983 (continued)
      - Automobile gas mileage (Box VF19)
      - Automobile industry (Box VF19)
      - Baby products (Box VF19)
      - Beatrice Foods (Box VF19)
      - Beneficial Management Co. (Box VF19)
      - Berkey Photo Inc. (Box VF19)
      - Bio-Chemic Research Foundation (Box VF19)
      - Bischop Industries (Box VF19)
      - Bissell (Box VF19)
      - Block Drug (Box VF19)
      - Boise Tire Co. (Box VF19)
      - Borden Inc. (Box VF19)
      - Bridgestone (Box VF19)
      - Bristol-Myers, (2 folders) (Box VF19)
      - Brown and Williamson (Box VF19)
      - Bubble Bath (Box VF19)
      - Bulova Watch Corp. (Box VF19)
      - C&H Sugar (Box VF19)
      - California Milk Board, (2 folders) (Box VF19)
    - Complaints, 1958-1983 (continued)
      - Campbell Soup Co. (Box VF20)
      - Career Search Inc. (Box VF20)
      - Carnation (Box VF20)
      - Carter Products Inc. (Box VF20)
      - CenCer Inc (Box VF20)
      - Chemway Corp (Box VF20)
      - Chrysler Motors (Box VF20)
      - Cinderella Finishing School (Box VF20)
      - Cleveland Consumer Reports (Box VF20)
      - Clorox (Box VF20)
      - Coca-Cola Company (Box VF20)
      - Cold remedies (Box VF20)
      - Colgate, (3 folders) (Box VF20)
      - Corporate image project, (2 folders) (Box VF20)
      - Commerce Drug (Box VF20)
      - Commercial Credit Cooperation (Box VF20)
    - Complaints, 1958-1983 (continued)
      - Computer Training Schools (Box VF21)
      - Cooga Mooga (Box VF21)
      - Cromwell Collier Macmillian (Box VF21)
      - Crown Central additives (Box VF21)
      - Cumberland Packing (Box VF21)
      - Dentrifrices (Box VF21)
      - Deodorants (Box VF21)
      - Dormeyer (Box VF21)
      - DuPont Corp. (Box VF21)
      - Ecology Corp. (Box VF21)
      - Encyclopedia Britannica (Box VF21)
      - Eggs (Box VF21)
      - ESB Co. (Box VF21)
      - Eversharp (Box VF21)
      - Executive Center Inc. (Box VF21)
      - Fedders Corp. (Box VF21)
      - Firestone Tire, (2 folders) (Box VF21)
      - Ford Motor Co. (Box VF21)
      - Furniture labeling (Box VF21)
      - Furniture manufacturers (Box VF21)
      - GAC Finance (Box VF21)
      - General Foods (Box VF21)
      - Glamorene (Box VF21)
      - Goodyear tires (Box VF21)
      - Grant Co. (Box VF21)
    - Complaints, 1958-1983 (continued)
      - Great Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co. (Box VF22)
      - Great Western United Co. (Box VF22)
      - G.R.I Corp. (Box VF22)
      - Grolier Inc. (Box VF22)
      - H&R Block (Box VF22)
      - Habana Cigar Co. (Box VF22)
      - Hearing aid industry (Box VF22)
      - Holiday Universal (Box VF22)
      - Hollywood Credit Clothing (Box VF22)
      - Hudson Pharmuceuticals (Box VF22)
      - Itt Continental Banking (Wonderbread), (2 folders) (Box VF22)
      - J.C. Penney (Box VF22)
      - Kent cigarettes (Box VF22)
      - Klien Co. (Box VF22)
      - Knox Gelatin (Box VF22)
      - Kodax Corp. (Box VF22)
      - Korvette (Box VF22)
      - Land sales (Box VF22)
      - Lanolin (Box VF22)
      - Lear Siegler (Box VF22)
      - Lever Brothers (Box VF22)
      - Libby-Owens (Box VF22)
      - Longines-Wittnauer (Box VF22)
    - Complaints, 1958-1983 (continued)
      - Magazines (Box VF23)
      - Mail order firms (Box VF23)
      - Mars, Inc. (Box VF23)
      - Mattel (Box VF23)
      - MCP Feeds (Box VF23)
      - McDonald's (Box VF23)
      - Matsushita (Box VF23)
      - Mayday Co. (Box VF23)
      - Medi-Hair (Box VF23)
      - Mennen (Box VF23)
      - Merck (Box VF23)
      - Morton Norwich Products (Box VF23)
      - Mouthwash (Box VF23)
      - National Commission on Egg Nutrition (Box VF23)
      - National Dynamics Corp. (Box VF23)
      - New York Jewelry Co. (Box VF23)
      - N.Y. Research Corp. (Box VF23)
      - Ocean Spray juice (Box VF23)
      - Pain relievers (Box VF23)
      - Pesticides (Box VF23)
      - Pet food (Box VF23)
      - Philip Morris (Box VF23)
      - Pfizer (Box VF23)
      - Pay-Less Drug Stores (Box VF23)
      - Plastics (Box VF23)
    - Complaints, 1958-1983 (continued)
      - Plough Inc. (Box VF24)
      - Policy planning protocol (Box VF24)
      - PoPeil Bros. (Box VF24)
      - Porter & Pietsch (Box VF24)
      - Proctor & Gamble, (2 folders) (Box VF24)
      - Proof of advertising (Box VF24)
      - Protein supplements (Box VF24)
      - Razors (Box VF24)
      - Rescinded complaints (Box VF24)
      - Ratke (Box VF24)
      - Readers Digest (Box VF24)
      - R.J. Reynolds (Box VF24)
      - Revere Chemical Corp. (Box VF24)
    - Complaints, 1958-1983 (continued)
      - Revco Discount Drugs (Box VF25)
      - Rhodes Pharmacal (Box VF25)
      - St. Regis Paper Co. (Box VF25)
      - S.A.M.E (Box VF25)
      - Sears (Box VF25)
      - Shampoo (Box VF25)
      - Sharp Electronic Corp. (Box VF25)
      - Irma Shorell (Box VF25)
      - Simon & Shuster (Box VF25)
      - Skil-Weave (Box VF25)
      - Soap and detergent (Box VF25)
      - S.O.U.P. (Box VF25)
      - Sperry-Hutchinson (Box VF25)
      - Spiesel Inc. (Box VF25)
      - Standard Brands (Box VF25)
      - Standard Oil, (2 folders) (Box VF25)
      - Sterling Drugs (Box VF25)
      - STP oil treatments (Box VF25)
    - Complaints, 1958-1983 (continued)
      - Strickland Co. (Box VF26)
      - Sugar Association (Box VF26)
      - Sun Oil Co. (Box VF26)
      - Swift and Co. (Box VF26)
      - Swimming pools (Box VF26)
      - Television sets (Box VF26)
      - Telex hearing aids (Box VF26)
      - Tires (Box VF26)
      - Tommorow's Heritage (Box VF26)
      - Topper Corp. (Box VF26)
      - Toshiba America (Box VF26)
      - Toy manufacturers (Box VF26)
      - T.U.B.E. (Box VF26)
      - Union Carbide Corp. (Box VF26)
      - Use of puffery (Box VF26)
      - Volvo (Box VF26)
      - Vitamin Education Institute (Box VF26)
      - Warner-Lambert Co (Box VF26)
      - Wasem's Inc. (Box VF26)
      - Weiman Co. (Box VF26)
      - Whirlpool Corp. (Box VF26)
      - Williams Co. (Box VF26)
      - Yamaha (Box VF26)
      - Zales (Box VF26)
      - Zonite Products (Box VF26)
    - Hearings
      - Drugs (OTC)
        - Summaries, 1977 Mar.-Apr. (Box VF27)
        - Testimony, 1977 Feb. 26-Apr. 1, (1-6 of 9 folders) (Box VF27)
        - Testimony, 1977 Feb. 26-Apr. 1 (continued), (7-9 of 9 folders) (Box VF28)
      - Food
        - Chicago, 1976 (Box VF28)
        - Dallas, 1976 (Box VF28)
        - Petitions, 1975 (Box VF28)
        - San Francisco, 1976 (Box VF28)
        - Washington, D.C., 1976 (Box VF28)
    - Modern Advertising Practices
      - General, 1971, (3 folders) (Box VF28 (contiued))
      - Testimony, 1971
        - Abrams, George (Box VF29)
        - Achenbaum, Allen (Box VF29)
        - Adams, Whitney (Box VF29)
        - Arnold, Maxwell (Box VF29)
        - Banks, Seymour (Box VF29)
        - Barcus, Earle (Box VF29)
        - Bauer, Raymond (Box VF29)
        - Bell, Howard (Box VF29)
        - Bluestone, Stephen (Box VF29)
        - Braren, Warren (Box VF29)
        - Brazelton, T. Berry (Box VF29)
        - Buzzell, Robert (Box VF29)
        - Campbell-Ewald Company (Box VF29)
        - Capitman, William (Box VF29)
        - Cash, Norman (Box VF29)
        - Choate, Robert (Box VF29)
        - Claggett, William (Box VF29)
        - Condry, John (Box VF29)
        - Cook, C.W. (Box VF29)
        - Cousins, Norman (Box VF29)
        - Crichton, John (Box VF29)
        - Cummings, Barton (Box VF29)
        - Daly, John (Box VF29)
        - David, Miles (Box VF29)
        - DeLay, Robert (Box VF29)
        - Demsetz, Harold (Box VF29)
        - Dennison, David (Box VF29)
        - Dichter,Ernest (Box VF29)
        - Dillon, Thomas (Box VF29)
        - Dingell, John (Box VF29)
        - Engel, James (Box VF29)
        - Ennis, F. Beaven (Box VF29)
        - Frey, Lou (Box VF29)